<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dante Stellare</title>
    <link>https://dantestellare.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dante Stellare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.146.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dantestellare.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Lab: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://dantestellare.github.io/posts/lab-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dantestellare.github.io/posts/lab-intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-philosophy-of-the-lab&#34;&gt;The Philosophy of the Lab&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After years of intense work and research, I&amp;rsquo;m confident that I now have the means to share my most ambitious and passionate projects with you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Lab&lt;/strong&gt; will be exactly what its name implies: &lt;em&gt;our comfortable laboratory to examine, create, and break things!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will not dwell on this section, but if you&amp;rsquo;re curious about who I am and what I do, and have a few minutes of free time at hand, you just might have a look at the &amp;ldquo;About&amp;rdquo; section.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Temple: Foundation</title>
      <link>https://dantestellare.github.io/posts/temple-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dantestellare.github.io/posts/temple-intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-philosophy-of-the-temple&#34;&gt;The Philosophy of the Temple&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The body is not a vanity project; it is the hardware upon which the mind runs. A weak chassis cannot support a high-performance engine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s of ultimate necessity to treat our body with the importance it deserves, as it is &lt;em&gt;the means through which we express our will onto the world&lt;/em&gt;. In the same way that the mind must be trained to be as sharp as possible so that we can achieve our ultimate potential, the same goes for our vessel (quite philosophical, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?). Doing so will maximize everything we do, while bringing along some well-deserved self-esteem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dantestellare.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dantestellare.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-polymath&#34;&gt;The Polymath&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a dual-degree student in &lt;strong&gt;Computer Science&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Mathematics&lt;/strong&gt;, building at the intersection of computational reasoning and physical discipline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the next steps to my plan, once my two bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degrees are completed, I&amp;rsquo;ll eventually pursue post-baccalaureates in both &lt;strong&gt;Physics&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Data Science&lt;/strong&gt;, to eventually apply for a PhD in &lt;strong&gt;Astrophysics&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal is not just to learn, but to synthesize. To merge the rigor of &lt;strong&gt;Astrophysics&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Data Science&lt;/strong&gt; with the discipline of &lt;strong&gt;Elite Calisthenics&lt;/strong&gt;. So of course, you&amp;rsquo;ll see both the intellectual and physical aspects of my life here, hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to share what I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about, while I continuously grow and help others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
